{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"87/3",
			"answer":"87/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"96/4",
			"answer":"96/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"68/4",
			"answer":"68/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"81/9",
			"answer":"81/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"44/4",
			"answer":"44/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"28/7",
			"answer":"28/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"35/7",
			"answer":"35/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"49/7",
			"answer":"49/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"56/7",
			"answer":"56/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"63/7",
			"answer":"63/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
	]
}